visitwynn.com 2018-06-24

# Privacy Policy | Wynn Las Vegas & Encore Resort

This Privacy Policy outlines the information Wynn Resorts Holdings, LLC and its affiliates (“Wynn”) will collect and how that information will be used. This privacy policy applies to all websites owned or operated by Wynn or its affiliates, including "[wynnlasvegas.com](http://www.wynnlasvegas.com/)", "[wynnsocial.com](http://www.wynnsocial.com/)", "[wynnresorts.com](http://wynnresorts.com/)" and "[encorebostonharbor.com](http://encorebostonharbor.com/)".

**Information We Collect**

As appropriate, Wynn may collect personally identifiable information from you voluntarily to provide you with a particular service. We may ask you for information such as name, address, telephone number and email address.

**Public Activities**

We may offer you opportunities to engage in Public Activities on the websites owned or operated by Wynn (the "Site"). "Public Activities" are any actions you take on the Site that are designed to be visible to other users, including comments, recommendations, reviews, photo submissions, or any other items or content that you submit on the Site, as well as social media activity that references Wynn, any of its properties, or any activities taking place at one of Wynn’s properties. Any information you disclose in your Public Activities, along with your user name (if any), any social media handle, or any image or photo, becomes public and may be used by Wynn for online and offline promotional or commercial uses in any and all media. If you choose to engage in Public Activities, you should be aware that any personal information you submit can be read, collected, or used by other users of these areas, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.

Wynn has no responsibility to publish, take down, remove or edit any of your Public Activities or any of your submissions that are a result of your Public Activities. By choosing to participate in Public Activities, you are electing to share and display such Public Activities via the Site. Also, Public Activities may be included in RSS feeds, APIs and made available to other websites via other formats. As a result, your Public Activities may appear on other websites, blogs, or feeds.

**Cookies and Tracking Technologies**

Wynn uses cookies, tags, and other similar technologies. These technologies allow us to recognize your preference information, keep track of your purchases, remember your Wynn Red Card number and facilitate effective site administration. We use the information we collect to enhance your visit to our various websites and to provide you with information tailored to your needs.

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. These text files can be read by these websites and help to identify you when you return to a website. Cookies can be “persistent” or “session” cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your computer when you have gone offline, while session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your web browser.

To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to block and delete cookies, please visit <http://www.aboutcookies.org/>.

Your Internet browser(s) may offer you the option to refuse cookies; however, doing so may affect your use of some portions of Wynn’s and our partners' web services. Please refer to your browser options or other browser instructional materials to learn more about cookie management.

Wynn has also engaged third party tracking and advertising providers such as Doubleclick, Tealium, Visual IQ, Facebook, Derbysoft, and Google Analytics to act on Wynn's behalf to track and analyze your usage of our site through the use of cookies, pixel tags/web beacons, and similar technologies. These third parties collect, and share with us, as we may request, website usage information about visits to our sites, measure and research the effectiveness of our advertisements, track page usage and paths followed during visits through our sites, help us target our internet banner advertisements on our sites and on other sites, and track use of our internet banner advertisements and other links from our marketing partners' sites to our sites.

The information collected on Wynn’s behalf by these third parties does not contain your name, address, email address, or any other personally identifiable information. To see further information about cookies on delta.com and opt out of some as you choose, see the descriptions and links below. To learn about the available mechanisms for opting out of cookies and technologies related to interest-based advertising, see the descriptions and links below.

Our websites, whether accessed on a computer or a mobile device, are not at this time configured to read or respond to “do not track” settings or signals in your browser headings, which vary by browser provider. In lieu of a browser-based opt-out solution, we have identified below certain approved methods for placement of “opt-out” cookies. Our sites and those of our third-party advertisers or other vendors are configured to read and honor these opt-out cookies, so long as they are present on your computer. If you delete all cookies, you will need to reset your opt-out cookies. Specific instructions on how to do so follow. However, please be aware that Wynn does not control these opt-out processes.

When you use Wynn websites, a unique ID (which varies by device manufacturer and operating system) is read from or associated with your device to be used as an anonymous identifier for analytics and performance purposes. Google Analytics may collect and store the ID, or share the ID or other unique information with third parties.

We do not use information gathered within the app to serve you targeted advertisements. The “limit ad tracking” or similar advertising-related privacy settings offered by device manufacturers do not change how your device is tracked by Wynn.

**Interest Based Advertising and Analytics**

Our website uses third party analytics tools such as [Google Analytics Privacy Policy and Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/), [Quantcast Privacy Policy](https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/), [Doubleclick](https://support.google.com/dfp_premium/answer/2839090?hl=en), [Derbysoft](https://www.derbysoft.com/privacy-policy/), [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update), [Optimizely](https://www.optimizely.com/privacy/), [Adobe](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html), [The Trade Desk](https://www.thetradedesk.com/general/privacy-policy), [Tapad](https://www.tapad.com/privacy-policy), [LiveRamp](https://liveramp.com/privacy/), [Bing](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement), [Blue Kai](https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/bluekai-privacy-policy.html), [Lotome](https://www.lotame.com/about-lotame/privacy/), [Google Ad Words](https://policies.google.com/privacy) to help us better understand our customers as noted above. To learn more, click on the third party to view its privacy policy. 

Third party vendors, including Google and Quantcast, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our websites or other websites. Google's and Quantcast's use of advertising cookies enable them and their partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to Wynn sites and/or other sites on the internet. 

We provide links to resources for opting out of different types of online tracking and interest-based targeting.

**Browsing**

We do not collect personally identifiable information from your computer when you browse this website and request pages from our servers. Unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide us with personally identifiable information, we will not know your name, your email address, or any other personally identifiable information. When you request a page from our website, our servers log the information provided in the HTTP request header including the IP number, the time of the request, the URL of your request and other information that is provided in the HTTP header.

**Information Use Security and Storage of Information**

All personal and general information that reaches Wynn is stored on a secure server that resides behind firewalls designed to block unauthorized access from outside of Wynn. Because laws applicable to personal information vary by country, our hotels or other business operations may put in place additional measures that vary depending on the applicable legal requirements. It is the policy of Wynn to protect the confidentiality of any social security numbers collected by Wynn, to prohibit unlawful disclosure of any social security numbers collected by Wynn and to limit and/or restrict access to any social security numbers collected by Wynn. Information collected on the sites covered by this statement is generally processed and stored in the United States.

Wynn may share your personal information with our properties, subsidiaries and select third parties as we deem appropriate. Your personal information may also be disclosed if necessary to: (1) enforce our Website Agreement; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of the Company; (3) comply with a court order or other legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authorities, including but not limited to authorities that regulate gaming activities; or (4) governmental authorities, in the sole discretion of the Company, in exceptional circumstances, such as a national emergency, security concern, or other situation in which the Company deems such disclosure prudent.

Wynn uses the services of third parties, such as e-mail service providers and marketing companies that act as agents on behalf of Wynn. These parties are contractually prohibited from using personally identifiable information for any purpose other than for the purpose Wynn specifies. We do provide non-personally identifiable information to certain service providers for their use on an aggregated basis for the purpose of performing their contractual obligations to us. We prohibit the sale or transfer of personal information to entities outside of the Wynn family of companies for use without your approval.

**E-Mails About Special Offers/Promotions and Opt-Out**

It is our intention to send you only e-mail communications that will be useful to you and that you want to receive. These communications will relate to Wynn offers and/or the promotions of select, reputable third parties with whom Wynn has a strategic marketing relationship because they offer products or services that we believe would be of interest to you. We use a third-party e-mail service provider to send e-mails. This service provider is prohibited from using your e-mail address for any purpose other than to send Wynn related e-mail. When you receive an e-mail, you will be provided the choice to opt-out of future e-mails by following the instructions provided in the e-mail.

You may choose whether you provide your phone number to receive text messages or advertising phone calls from us or our agents that are made using an automatic telephone dialing system or an artificial or prerecorded voice. By providing your phone number and express consent, you are choosing to receive such messages until you withdraw your consent. Your consent to receive text messages or pre-recorded calls using an automatic telephone dialing system is not required to make a purchase. You may revoke your consent at any time by contacting us at [webmaster@wynnlasvegas.com](mailto:webmaster@wynnlasvegas.com).

**Use of Third-Party Internet Sites**

Third-party Internet sites and services accessible through Wynn have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Wynn has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions.

**The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

Wynn does not knowingly or intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from, or market to, individuals under the age of 21. Pursuant to law, persons under the age of 21 are not permitted to gamble at our properties or loiter in casino areas. Similarly, our websites are not intended for persons under the age of 21. Persons under the age of 21 are not allowed to use our site in any fashion, so the provisions of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act do not apply to Wynn websites.

**Use By EU Residents**

You are expressly prohibited from using Wynn’s websites if you are located within the European Union.

**Privacy Rights of Certain US Residents**

If you are a Nevada resident, California resident, or a resident of another state with similar privacy rights, you have the right to request information from us regarding the categories of personal information that we collect and, if applicable, the manner in which we share certain categories of personal information with third parties, in addition to the rights set forth above. Under applicable law, you have the right to send us a request at the designated address listed below to receive the following information:

  * The categories of information we collected;
  * The categories of third parties with whom your information may have been shared; and
  * A disclosure concerning whether a third party may have collected information about your online activies in connection with your use of Wynn’s websites.

If you are a California resident, you additionally have the right to names and addresses of the third parties that received the information for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year and, if the nature of the third party’s business cannot be determined from their name, examples of the products or services marketed.

This information may be provided in a standardized format that is not specific to you. Requests should be sent to [webmaster@wynnlasvegas.com](mailto:webmaster@wynnlasvegas.com).

**Privacy Statement Changes**

In the future, we may need to change this privacy statement. All changes will be made here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Accordingly, we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to become aware of any changes that may have occurred. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the “Effective Date” below.

**Contact Us**

by email: [webmaster@wynnlasvegas.com](mailto:webmaster@wynnlasvegas.com)

by writing to us at: Wynn Las Vegas 
  * 3131 Las Vegas Blvd. South  
Las Vegas, NV 89109  
Attn: Guest Relations  

Effective Date: 05/25/2018
